screenseven.com 2012-05-29

# Download Games | Free & Safe PC Game Downloads at SCREENSEVEN

Viva Media wants you to understand how we use the information you provide to us. We believe that you should have the right to approve the use of that information. As technology changes, it will become necessary for Viva Media to make changes to its privacy policy and procedures. All such changes will be posted to this site.

**How We Gather Information**

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), unique identifiers and demographic information (like their zip/postal code, age, or income level). Contact information from the registration forms is used to provide information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Unique identifiers are collected from Web site visitors for use as account numbers in our record system.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. We also use this data to send host sites their royalty payments. This data is not available for sale to any outside entity.

Additionally, users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) on non-secure areas of Viva Media’s site, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in the user's communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Viva Media.

We work closely with our affiliates, and in some cases we offer services or sell documents jointly with these affiliates. If you purchase documents or services that are provided jointly by Viva Media and one of its affiliates, we share our customer information with that affiliate with respect to your purchase.

We also employ agents to fulfill other functions on our behalf, such as providing marketing assistance, analyzing data, preparing and maintaining site content, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. These agents have access to customer information as required in order to help them perform their functions on our behalf, but they are not allowed to use that information for any other purpose.

We receive and store certain information whenever you visit our website. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site, and to help identify you. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes. Any information you voluntarily provide to us is used for such purposes as customizing your shopping experience, allowing us to respond to your requests and comments, and improving our website.

Viva Media reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of our site(s) and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. Viva Media will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. Also, you should be aware that Viva Media may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through a Viva Media site. Viva Media is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and you should check the applicable privacy policy of such third party when providing personally identifiable information.

**Information Gathered from Minors**

We encourage children visiting our site to ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to us or to anyone else over the Internet. Any such information collected by Viva Media from children will be used for participation and feedback purposes, together with any other purposes that will be described where the information is collected, and will not be transferred to any third party. Customers purchasing goods or services on Viva Media’s site(s) must be at least 18 years of age.

**How We Use this Information**

Unless you have opted to allow us to do so Viva Media will not use your email address to send you news about or updates to Viva Media’s site(s), to forward special offers or ads from our affiliates and to respond to customer service issues or comments and questions received from you. Upon request, Viva Media will allow any user to “opt out” of further promotional contacts at any time. If you do not wish to receive notification of special offers or news and/or updates to our site(s), please email Viva Media at [mail@viva-media.com](mailto:mail@viva-media.com).

Credit card or other financial information that is collected is used for billing and payment purposes for products and services you have ordered through Viva Media’s site(s), and is submitted to the appropriate financial institution in order to process your credit card transaction, and will not be provided to any other person or party. All other private information submitted by you is confidential. You can update or delete your private information at any time by emailing Viva Media at mail@viva-media.com. However, it may be impossible to delete a user’s information without some residual information being left in our customer database due to backups and records of deletions.

Information submitted by our affiliates is used for the purposes of maintaining the business relationship between Viva Media and its affiliates and will not be provided to any third party. Our affiliates are not provided with any access to private information you have provided to us, whether or not such information was provided in connection with the purchase of goods or services from an affiliate’s site.

**Use of Cookies**

You should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of Viva Media’s internet servers or through the use of “cookies.” “Cookies” are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user’s ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a user’s system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Users should be aware that Viva Media cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for Viva Media. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the Viva Media Site.

**Transfer of Customer Information**

Customer information is a valuable business asset. If for any reason Viva Media transfers or divests itself of its business assets, our customer information will be transferred as one of the business assets.

**Release of Information When Required**

Viva Media will release customer information to the appropriate authorities if we are required to do so by law. Viva Media will also release such information if we feel it is necessary in order to protect our rights or the rights of our customers, affiliates, partners, or any other party, and for purposes of protection from fraud and credit risk.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at [mail@viva-media.com](mailto:mail@viva-media.com) or at Viva Media LLC, 580 Broadway, Suite 604, New York, NY 10012. Any dispute arising between you and Viva Media with respect to privacy is subject to the terms and conditions of use and this privacy statement, including limitations on damages, arbitration, and application of the laws of New York, NY.

The foregoing policies are effective as of 08/23/05. Viva Media reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
